all right what up alright so we're in
the common in our backyard that's the
more of Khmer I this is not gonna be a
long periscope we found a weed whacker
in the hobbit door and you lost your
cord we're going to attempt to grill
grilling might happen there's a grill we
found it but we had to whack away to it
is it an IOT weed whacker Oh Oh quality
I'll plug in the ethernet port yeah it's
good we need wireless power like the
essential phone power reason it that's
true well we actually have 71 people
right now look at arrows it's also a
dilapidated Toyota Prius
so this is the Wow we have 113 people
holy shit what's up with all the feel
good we got some more extension cord all
right so no no what you're doing it real
nice
[Music]
now with safety goggles it's OSHA but
where's the new Accord it's in front
we're taking the new Accord to go
shopping here's my motorcycle it's like
the DeLorean at the end it back to the
future but when they hide it in the
bushes shoes are sad Prius Wow how are
you all here that's that's the bundle of
wires powering the 3d printers here's
the Prius is flat tire sad do you guys
see my slam you guys see twitch slam oh
yeah no let's whack that let's whack
that table we're gonna eat outside like
civilized memorials these are cool first
we're working to come a high you get to
do yard work
[Music]
happy Memorial Day everybody
look at that equality wagging alright yo
look I'm wearing it I'm wearing a
brightly colored shirt whoo all right
I'm gonna go we got we got some some
Memorial Day celebrating to do
happy Memorial Day from everybody to
come AI should we plug the shop should
we plug the shop yet check out the
Memorial Day sale shop kama dolly eye
everything's for sale that's not we
didn't add any money it's always for
sale it's over sale um no but seriously
uh I'm gonna have a good time with your
with your families your significant
others your co-workers whoever you
choose to spend this Memorial Day with
there's no Memorial Day sale that was
fake news Gloria Borger never would have
reported that no one 2088 nan midnight
black eons are never coming back
cycle yeah boys not on sale for sale
that's right you can buy for eons
it's a Memorial Day sale all right later
scobie's